Now listen, yo!
People put your guns up
Mazu ore ga run dat
Hashirimawatte yatsura o gun shot
Brand new sound sou still survival
Here come the sound boy kono sekai ni ikiro
Chiryoku tairyoku to un ga mau ze! Flow
Fukuranda ataman naka wa zakkubaran nan da
Savannah de Banna ni wanpan
Kantan knockout kan kan kan
One time for your mind ikinuke
Around the world
Tsukimatou no sa itsu no itami mo
Kedakai kami no mawari mo ima karimono
Makareta tane mo hana sakeba dare no
Ikite uchikomu shinnen no ya o more more more
Ikisaki ni yasuragi wa nai
Tachi na sa don't give up the fight
Ima sou kono shunkan mo die die die
Big shooter ikiisoide blazing
Beat you up kirihiraite break
Shot shooter ikiisoida crazy
Shoujun au shikin kyori de break
Big shooter ikiisoide blazing
Beat you up kirihiraite break
Shot shooter ikiisoida crazy
Shoujun au shikin kyori de break
（計(けい)）あっ…
岸本(きしもと)さん？
Miss Kishimoto?
うわぁ… かわいい
She's so cute!
But why's she in front of my place?
でも なんで俺ん家(ち)の前に？
（岸本）うん…？ ウワッ！
（計）ウワッ！
（岸本）あっ… これ
（計）あっ！
Here...
（岸本）そう　玄野(くろの)君の上着
貸してもらったでしょう？
See, you let me borrow your jacket, right?
着替えるとき
部屋に落としちゃったみたい
I guess this must've fallen out in
my room when I was changing.
Student ID Holder
2000-2001
Kei Kurono
I guess this must've fallen out in
my room when I was changing.
こ… これを届けるために？
（岸本）う… うん
You came here just to deliver this?
Yeah.
（岸本）じゃ… じゃあね
See you.
Could I have a glass of water?
ちょっと お水もらえるかな？
えっ？ い… いいけど
Yeah, sure.
All Right!
Upsy-daisy, upsy-daisy, upsy-daisy...
（鉄男(てつお)）ほ～ら… ほ～ら… お～…
（赤ん坊の笑い声）
Hey!
Upsy-daisy, upsy-daisy, upsy-daisy...
（妻）ねえ！
（鉄男）ほ～ら！
ほ～ら！
Upsy-daisy, upsy-daisy,
upsy-daisy, upsy-daisy...
I've told you to cut the engine
when you're near the house!
Upsy-daisy, upsy-daisy,
upsy-daisy, upsy-daisy...
家の近くじゃエンジン切ってって
言ってるでしょう！
（携帯電話の着信音）
近所のおばさん にらむんだからね
Upsy-daisy, upsy-daisy,
upsy-daisy, upsy-daisy...
The neighborhood ladies give me
dirty looks, you know?
Upsy-daisy, upsy-daisy,
upsy-daisy, upsy-daisy...
Kamikaze
What? Yeah.
（鉄男）ああ？　おう
Kamikaze
うん　ああ いいよ
What? Yeah... Okay.
I'm going down to the store
to buy some cigarettes.
ちょっと
コンビニでタバコ買ってくる
じゃ ついでに牛乳買ってきて
（鉄男）おう 分かった　牛乳な
While you're there, pick up some milk.
Gotcha, milk it is.
（エンジン音）
もう！
Honestly!
Tea's okay, right?
お茶でいいよね？
（岸本）あっ… ありがとう
Thanks. Water would've been fine.
お水でよかったのに
（計）あ～… いいから いいから
No problem, no problem.
So you live alone?
１人暮らしなの？
（計）うん
Yeah...
あっ でもさ 電話くれりゃ
こっちから取りに行ったのに
But if you'd given me a call,
I would've come by to pick it up.
あっ… 腹減ってるの？
Are you hungry?
何かあったの？
（岸本）えっ？
Did something happen?
Not really. I was just hungry, that's all.
別に… ただ おなかすいてたから
Sorry. This was your dinner, wasn't it, Kurono?
ごめんね　これ
玄野君の晩ご飯だったんでしょう？
（計）うわ “玄野君”だと？
名前呼ばれちゃったよ 名前！
"Kurono"! She called me by my name!
By my name!
いいんだよ そんなの
すぐコンビニあるから
Don't worry about that. There's
a convenience store close by.
そう？
（計）うん
Really?
Yeah.
（岸本）それじゃ…
Okay, well...
I'm really sorry about showing up unexpectedly.
ホントに ごめんね 突然
じゃあね！
Bye!
What was that all about?
何だったんだ？
Green Tea
あれ？
Hm?
Is it against the rules to keep
cats and dogs at this apartment?
このアパートさ…
猫とか犬とか飼っちゃダメなの？
はぁ？ 飼ってる人いるけど…
Some people here have them.
そっか… じゃあさ
（計）えっ？
I see. So, well...
Yeah?
Would you consider keeping one?
飼ってくれないかな？
One of what?
（計）何を？
はぁ？
（岸本）ごめん！ ダメだよね
What?!
I'm sorry! It won't work, then.
No!
いや ダメじゃない！
ダメじゃない！ ダメじゃない！
It's all right! It's all right! It's all right!
全然ＯＫ！
It's A-OK!
本当？
（計）うん
Really?
Yeah. But what do you mean by "keep"?
ていうか… か… “飼う”って？
I mean, like a pet.
だから ペットみたいに…
ダメだったら しょうがないけど
But if you can't, that's okay.
いや ダメじゃない　ダメじゃない
No! I can. I can.
I'm sorry. What I'm saying must sound strange.
（岸本）ごめん
私 おかしなこと言ってるよね
Yeah... I mean no! Not at all.
At least, I don't think so.
うん　あっ… いや そんなことない
そんなことはない …と思う
This could mean...
これって… これって… これって！
This could mean!
THIS COULD MEAN!
（カヨ）大丈夫よ　亮太(りょうた)も
泊まりたいって言ってるんだし
It's all right.
Even Ryota says he wants to spend the night.
幼稚園？
そんなの１日ぐらい休んだって
どうってこと…
Kindergarten? They won't care
if he's absent for just one day.
お前だって 子供のころは
よく休んだじゃないの
When you were a kid, you were
absent a lot too, remember?
（亮太）ブルルル… ドッカ～ン！
Bam!
あっ！ 事故です！ 事故です！
救急車 呼んでください
There's been an accident! There's been
an accident! Call an ambulance!
ピーポー ピーポー…
Whee-woo! Whee-woo! Whee-woo!
（カヨ）はいはい　あしたの夜には
ちゃんと そっちに送っていくから
Yes, yes, I'll be sure to bring him back
tomorrow night. Bye now!
Whee-woo! Whee-woo! Whee-woo!
Yes, yes, I'll be sure to bring him back
tomorrow night. Bye now!
じゃあね
（受話器を置く音）
Grandma, what did Mom say?
（亮太）
おばあちゃん お母さん 何だって？
You can stay here tonight.
今日は ここに泊まっていいって
（亮太）やったー！
All right!
（カヨ）あしたは どこ行きたい？
Where do you want to go tomorrow?
（亮太）日出台(ひのでだい)デパート！
トラックのミニカー買ってほしい
Hinodedai Department Store.
I want you to buy me a mini toy truck.
（カヨ）
はいはい　何でも買ってあげますよ
Yes, dear, I'll buy you whatever you want.
（加藤(かとう)）歩(あゆむ)…
Ayumu...
What happened to your neck?
お前 首のところ それって…
（歩）いいよ
（加藤）またなのか？
It's okay.
It happened again?
It's nothing.
（歩）何でもないって
兄ちゃん
叔母さんを悪く言っちゃダメだよ
Masaru, you shouldn't say
bad things about our aunt.
I don't think she's a bad person.
（歩）悪い人じゃないと思うんだ
ただ 僕たちみたいなのが
急に転がり込んできたから…
It's just that we showed up here
unexpectedly, and...
I think she's just a little irritated, that's all.
それで ちょっと
イライラしてるだけだと思うんだ
But that doesn't mean that
it's all right for her to hit you.
（加藤）だから暴力を
振るっていいってことには―
ならないだろう
Anyway, it doesn't matter. I'm all right.
とにかく いいんだ
僕は平気だから
But even so, the president made a rash
remark this time, wouldn't you say?
（キャスター）それにしても
今回の大統領の発言は―
軽率なのではないですか？
（解説者）そうですね
Yes. I wonder what he takes
the world for, anyway?
彼は 世界を
何だと思っているんでしょうかね
（キャスター）
近々 行われる大統領選挙に―
This will no doubt have some effect
on the upcoming presidential election.
何らかの影響が出るのは
間違いないでしょうね
I wonder if it'd be all right...
いいかな？
（計）何が？
For what?
シャワー浴びたいんだけど
I'd like to take a shower.
シャワー？ ああ どうぞ どうぞ…
A shower?! Be my guest!
ツイてる！ 最近ツイてる！
Yes! Lately Lady Luck's been smiling on me!
I have my doubts, but...
疑問はあるけど
今 深くは考えますまい！
Let's not dwell on those for now!
（メンバー）
マジか？ アハハハッ…
Tetsu, has the wife been bitching at you again?
（春哉(はるや)）鉄ちゃん また
カミさんに何か言われたろう？
Not really.
（鉄男）別に…
Then why are you out buying milk?
（春哉）じゃ…
なんで牛乳なんか買ってるんよ？
Shut up!
（鉄男）…るせえよ
（男性）そこのダニども！
Hey, you punks!
Shut up!
（春哉）ああ？
（男性）周りの家に迷惑じゃないか
You're disturbing the people around here.
Quiet down!
（男性）静かにしなさい！
（欣二(きんじ)）何だ？ このオヤジ
What's with this guy?
（春哉）女房持ちのゾクってのも
つれえよなぁ
It must be tough being a biker with a wife.
（鉄男）うるせえ！
（康介(こうすけ)）殺すか？
Shut up!
Do we kill him?
Let's do it, Tetsu.
（春哉）やるぜ 鉄ちゃん
（男の子）あっ…
（春哉）ウワッ！
ウッ…
（欣二・康介）てめえ！
Bastard!
うわぁ！
What?
（岸本）なに？
（計）あっ… な… 何でもない
Nothing, just...
ちょっと その…
メシとかジュースとか…
I'm going out to buy us dinner
and something to drink, and, and,
あ～ そうそう
お菓子とか買ってくるから
and some snacks and stuff.
Thanks.
（岸本）ありがとう
Green Tea
（春哉）あっ…
オヤジのパンツ下ろしちゃえよ
Pull down his pants!
（男性）わ… 悪かった　悪かった
（春哉）遅(おせ)えっつうの
I'm sorry!
It's too late for that!
（康介）
ハハッ… ちっちゃそう こいつ
I bet he's got a small one!
Most Wanted Criminals
Missing Persons
I wonder...
あの子…
Most Wanted Criminals
Missing Persons
Maybe she ran away and has no place to go.
家出してきて 行く所ないとか？
Beware of Dog
Maybe she ran away and has no place to go.
Come to think of it, she asked me
to "keep" her, but...
そういえば…
Come to think of it, she asked me
to "keep" her, but...
飼ってくれなんて言ってたけど…
飼育？
"Tend to her"?
Or maybe...
…ていうか …ていうか
Maybe tonight's my chance to score.
もしかして 今夜 俺は…
With a cute girl like her!
あんな かわいい子と…
マジかよ おい！
Gimme a break!
（計）ウオ～ッ！ すごすぎる～！
This is TOO much!
フゥ…
お風呂 入りたかった…
I really wanted to take a bath.
The people who are here
came out of a fax machine.
（西(にし)）ここにいる人間は
ファクスから出てきた人間なんだよ
（岸本の母親）
お姉ちゃんが お風呂で倒れたのよ
Your big sister fell in the bathtub.
It was very sudden.
We're copies.
（西）コピーだ
The original really is dead.
オリジナルは本当に死んでる
（母親）あっ 大丈夫よ　生きてる
The original really is dead.
Don't worry, she's alive.
ファクスから…
（母親）さっき意識が戻ったの
A fax machine...
She just regained consciousness.
We're copies.
（西）コピーだ
（母親）生きてる！
We're copies.
Alive... Alive... Alive...
Dead.
生きてる！ 生きてる！
（西）死んでる
Alive... Alive... Alive...
死んでる
Dead.
（メンバー）ほら 行くぞ！
Your old man's friggin' weak! What a dork!
（春哉）
お前(めえ)の親父(おやじ) 超弱(よえ)え　カッコ悪い
あんま ゾクなめてんじゃねえぞ
You shouldn't mess with the boys!
Hey, kid!
（鉄男）おい ガキ
父ちゃんみてえに
情けねえ男になるんじゃねえぞ
Don't grow up to be a pathetic loser
like your dad!
（計）あ～あ…
Then Torao the Truck thought,
（カヨ）そのとき
トラックのトラ夫(お)君は思いました
"No, no, at this rate,
I'll be asleep at the wheel."
“ダメだ ダメだ　このままじゃ
居眠り運転になってしまう”
With all his might, Torao rubbed his eyes
and flew down the highway.
トラ夫君は一生懸命 目をこすり
高速道路をバビュ～ンと…
You really are a darling.
かわいいねえ ホントに
Wah-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta... Wah-ta!
（加藤）
“アタタタ… アターッ！”
"You are already dead," is it?
“お前は もう死んでいる”か
The original really is dead.
本体…
オリジナルは本当に死んでる
The people who are here
came out of a fax machine.
ここにいる人間は
ファクスから出てきた人間なんだよ
Kei..."You are already dead."
計ちゃん…
お前は もう死んでるってさ
So what would you do, Kei?
どうする？ 計ちゃん…
Green Tea PET Bottle x 2300 yen
Young Jump 280 yen
今 どこで何してる？
Green Tea PET Bottle x 2300 yen
Young Jump 280 yen
Where are you and what are you doing now?
Green Tea PET Bottle x 2300 yen
Young Jump 280 yen
Ultra-thin Condoms 1,000 yen
そこで人の顔見るな！
Don't pick NOW to look me in the face!
I went ahead and bought Young Jump
so I could buy the condoms!
コンドームのノリで
ヤンジャン買っちまった！
（鉄男）あんなぁ…
タバコ持ってんなら言えって
Hey, if you had cigarettes,
you should've said something.
Wicked Demon Rasetsu
Hey, if you had cigarettes,
you should've said something.
Wicked Demon Rasetsu
Then I wouldn't have had
to go out and buy them.
わざわざ
買いに行くことなかったろうが
Then I wouldn't have had
to go out and buy them.
Don't you lie to me.
ウソつかないでさぁ…
走りたければ
“走ってくる”って言いなよ
If you want to go out riding, just say,
"I'm going out riding."
牛乳
（妻）冷蔵庫 入れといて
Here's the milk.
Put it in the fridge.
いいんだよ これで
Things are fine the way they are.
あ… あれ？
What?
（岸本）
ありがとう　いいお湯でした
Thanks.
I had a nice bath.
うん？
（計）いや…
Nothing.
な… なんで また服着てんの？
なんで？
Why is she back in her clothes?
Why...
（漫才師）なんでやねん！
Why the heck?
今のナイス ツッコミ！
フフフフッ…
That was a nice comeback.
家出か何か？
So did you run away or something?
シカトされてるし
この距離も なに？
She's ignoring me.
And what's with this distance?
I didn't think the mood would be like this.
思ってたのと雰囲気 違うぞ…
But still, forcing myself on her?
でもなぁ… 力ずくってのもな
That'd be too much like porn.
それじゃＡＶみたいだもんな
やっぱ こういうのって
愛とかないとダメなんかなって
I guess there's got to be love or something
when you do stuff like this.
そんなのムリじゃん
That's just not possible.
ゆうべ会ったばっかだし…
（岸本）ねえ…
We only just met last night.
Hey.
だったら いきなり…
If so, maybe I could just force her down?
（岸本）
ねえ もうひとつ布団ある？
Hey, do you have another futon mattress?
If so, maybe I could just force her down?
えっ？ あ… ああ… ない
No...
そっか…
Oh.
（計）
そうだ　ないぞ 布団！ ラッキー！
That's right, I don't have another
futon mattress. Score!
I see.
そっか…
うわ 向こうも意識してんぜ
She's aware of it too.
来る！ ついに そのときが…
At long last, the time has come!
そうだ そうだ　布団忘れてた
Right. Right, I forgot about the futon mattress.
Can I sleep in the same bed as you?
一緒のベッドで寝ていい？
そうだね　しょうがないよね
いっか まあ…
Oh, yeah. I guess there's no other choice.
Sure, I guess.
I'm going to the bathroom
before I get in bed.
寝る前に おトイレ行ってくるね
All right! Things are starting to heat up!
やったー！
ヤバイぜ これ　まじヤバイ！
Definitely!
うわ… こんなんなんだ？
So this is what they're like.
じゃ 寝よっか
Okay, guess it's time for bed.
I'm sorry, could you turn the other way?
ごめん　あっち向いてて…
Okay.
My skirt and stuff would get
all wrinkled if I slept in them.
（岸本）このままじゃ
スカートとかシワになっちゃうから
I see.
（計）そっか
Good night.
おやすみなさい
（計）おやすみなさい…
Good night.
あれ？
What?
You know...
あのさ…
（岸本）どうしたの？
What's wrong?
（計）あ～…
この状況で何もしないのかな 俺は
Am I just supposed to do nothing
in a situation like this?
What was it you wanted to do?
（岸本）何かしたいの？
（計）エッチ…
S... e... x...
I'm your pet.
（岸本）私は 玄野君のペット
You know, a pet.
ペットなんだよ？
ペットとはエッチしないじゃん
You don't have sex with your pet.
What the hell does THAT mean?! What a gyp!
（計）何じゃ そりゃ！ 詐欺だ
あっ…
俺 い… 犬 実家で飼っててさ
I used to have a dog at home.
抱き締めたり
チューしてたりは してた
And I used to give it hugs and kisses.
（岸本）じゃ いいよ…
Oh, all right then.
Really?
（計）ホント？
Yeah.
や… やった…
All right!
（計）うわ 気持ちいい
This feels good!
（岸本）私ね…
I...
子供のころ 元気がよくて
よく 体に傷を作ってたんだよね
When I was a kid, I was pretty active,
and I used to cut myself up a lot.
傷？
（岸本）うん　傷…
Cut yourself?
Yeah, cut myself...
でもね 全部ないの
But all of them are gone.
The cut that needed eight stitches,
the cut from two months ago...
８針縫った傷も ２か月前の傷も
それから
この間 自分で切った手首の傷も
And the cuts I made to my wrists the other day.
When I went home...
（岸本）帰ったら… 家に帰ったら
When I got back home...
まだ 私がいたの
I still existed.
私って なに？ 何なの？
What am I? What am I?
私には居場所がない
帰る家もない　親もいない
I have no place to go!
No house to come home to.
No parents...
I'm sorry, Kurono.
ごめんね 玄野君
Now's not the time for me to be
throwing away my virginity.
バージン捨ててる場合じゃなくて…
I'm sorry. I really am.
ごめんね ホントに
This morning, once again, we have a follow-up
on those missing high school boys.
（リポーター）さて 今朝も また
あの“高校生失踪事件”の続報です
The two boys suddenly disappeared
in the subway.
地下鉄で こつ然と姿を消した
２人の男子高校生
その後 当番組でも―
Since then, we've tried to investigate the incident
from many different angles on this show,
さまざまな角度から
検証してみましたが―
but the identities of the missing high school
students have yet to be determined.
行方不明となっている高校生の
身元は いまだ判明しておりません
However, we believe that tracing the sales route
of the plastic umbrella and the adult magazine
しかし このビニール傘と
ヘアヌード写真集の販売ルートから
will turn up some promising leads.
有力な手がかりが
つかめるものと思われまして―
今後 更なる 意外な展開が
待ち受けているものと思われます
And we believe we can expect
even more surprising developments.
Where did these boys vanish to?
本当に どこへ
消えてしまったのでしょうか？
以上 現場から お伝えいたしました
That is all.
Reporting from the scene...
In the end, my virginity remained intact.
（計）結局 童貞喪失ならず
次の呼び出し いつかな？
I wonder when we'll be called next?
Hajimari wa dare demo junshin muku na baby
Nigai mi kajitte mo kujikecha
dame yo walk straight
Satta koto da kedo ame no naka
zukizuki itamu yo
I'm lonely as floating ice
Yaseta yubi ni kiss o shite
Naita anata o omoidasu yo
Kore de owari da to shite mo
Saigo no kiss wa wasurenai yo
Wasurenai yo
Kare no kiss o wasurenai yo
（西）ＤＶ 牛乳 ストーカー
Domestic violence...
Milk...
Stalker...
Shoplifting...
万引き ゾク アイドル 過保護
Biker...
Idol...
Overprotection...
Shall we get down to business?
そろそろ やりますか
Next time: "We're After You"
次回 “狙ってるぜ”